(dramatic music plays)
La vita sbocciò da radici sante,
Un amore cullato, dolce e costante.
Un sogno sussurrato sotto la pioggia,
E una preghiera nata dalla piaga.
pain.
Nei nostri inni, Cottolengo, sei grazia,
Nei nostri salmi, una luce che mai si spegne,
Nelle nostre voci, il tuo amore scorre ancora,
Dio ci donò il Cottolengo —
Per sempre cantiamo: Deo Gracias.
Deo Gracias.
Deo,
Gracias.
Cottolengo—il nome che chiamiamo casa,
home. A shelter when
the thunder roars. A
vase where delicate hearts are
held. A dream that time
could never
fold.
Nei nostri inni, Cottolengo, sei grazia,
Nei nostri salmi, una luce che mai si spegne,
Nelle nostre voci, il tuo amore scorre ancora,
Dio ci donò il Cottolengo —
Per sempre cantiamo: Deo Gracias.
Deo gratias.
Oh, Deo
Gracias.
We are the roses time can't fade.
We are the joy Cottolengo
dreamt. We are the love etched
in Cottolengo's heart. Through
every tear, joy and whispered prayer, we
still remain roses of
Cottolengo. In our
hymns, Cottolengo you are
grace in our psalms. A light no
night erases. In our voices
your love still flows. God gave us Cottolengo
Forever we sing Deo
Gracias.
Caritas Christi urget
nos. With Cottolengo,
Deo
Gracias.
Deo gratias.
Gratias.